<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam&apos;s Food Blog</title>
    <description>Memories through nourishments.</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 02:52:59 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 02:52:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Late Night Bite</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some nights, I enjoy walking out to this modern local izakaya restaurant. They close pretty late, which makes it perfect for a late night snack. What makes this place unique is their dedication to brewing their own teas and constantly experimenting with new dishes on the menu. I like to order their mocktail Shiso Dry as my drink. As for meal spicy tuna onigiri with a bowl of miso soup is enough for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just want to show my appreciation and admiration for this place. But you guys will never find it! I regularly come here during the weekends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/late-night-bite/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/late-night-bite/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pizza by The Water</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We took our annual road trip to Baja California Sur to visit the beach and play some golf. I like how this location is farther from the city compared to other resorts. I really enjoyed the sweet and savory sauce on the pizza with shredded chicken. After eating, I fell asleep, and half of my legs ended up getting tanned.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/pizza-by-the-water/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/pizza-by-the-water/</guid>
        
        <category>Pizza</category>
        
        <category>Cabo</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chicken Alfredo at Marmalade Cafe</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I was in the area and decided to try this café chain since I’d heard a lot about it. The atmosphere felt a bit dull, and the floor looked like it hadn’t been swept in a while, but it might have just been a temporary lapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food took a little longer than expected, but I didn’t mind since I was nursing my orange juice while waiting. The portion size was reasonable, and I appreciated the sauce’s consistency. However, I was disappointed by how dry the chicken was.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/chicken-alfredo-at-marmalade-cafe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/chicken-alfredo-at-marmalade-cafe/</guid>
        
        <category>Pasta</category>
        
        <category>California</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peking Duck Salad at MOT 32</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t usually like spending time in the casino because cigarette smoke tends to trigger my allergies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Peking duck salad was quite good—I especially enjoyed the dressing and fresh vegetables paired with the duck. The price of the salad is debatable, given that they used a citrus truffle dressing. While I thought it was good, it’s not something I’d go out of my way to eat again. There’s also a business casual dress code, which I understand, but it’s not exactly a place I’d choose to dine alone again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/peking-duck-salat-at-mot-32/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/peking-duck-salat-at-mot-32/</guid>
        
        <category>Salad</category>
        
        <category>Las Vegas</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Berry Berry at Beignet Spot</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It was bum hot outside, so I decided to cool off at a beignet spot after a business meeting. Since it was mid-afternoon, the place was nearly empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cashier greeted me warmly as I walked in, and I ordered the Berry Berry. While waiting, I peered through a large window into the kitchen to watch the beignets being made. When my order arrived, I was surprised by the large portion size. The assortment of berries and the generous amount of jam were delightful. Although the whipped cream was a bit much on my sweet tooth, it still paired well with the beignets. Thankfully, there was a water station nearby, which helped washed out the sweetness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn’t come back alone, but I’d definitely return with a friend to share the portions with.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/berry-berry-at-beignet-spot/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/berry-berry-at-beignet-spot/</guid>
        
        <category>Dessert</category>
        
        <category>California</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beef Bowl Noodles at Bowltiful Lanzhou</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I arrived to Melbourne pretty late and most restaurants were closed. But Bowltiful was open and I was pleasantly surprised by the flavor of the chili and noodles. Since it was rather late, it allowed me to enjoy the atmosphere of the place.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/beef-bowl-noodles-at-bowltiful-lanzhou/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/beef-bowl-noodles-at-bowltiful-lanzhou/</guid>
        
        <category>Noodle</category>
        
        <category>Melbourne</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not Eelaborate</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After my long train ride, I visited a deer park and got to feed the wildlife. There were so many restaurants to choose from but I was craving eel. I really like the soup mixed in with the rice and fish. The wasabi threw me off since I don’t normally have it served this way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would recommend this place if you want to find a quiet restaurant to eat at, and wouldn’t mind finding a few small fish bones. Eels are known to carry lots of tiny bones it’s inevitable that you’ll find it in a lot of places.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/not-elaborate/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/not-elaborate/</guid>
        
        <category>Fish</category>
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pork Cutlet</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My friend introduced me to their favorite local restaurant. It was my first time having a pork cutlet served in a pan. The sauce made it slightly soggy, but the tangy, savory flavor was banger. I was really happy with the meal, and I’d love to try a different item on the menu next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/pork-cutlet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/pork-cutlet/</guid>
        
        <category>Meat</category>
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sleuths and Sweets</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I visited my friend in Japan, and we had some decent crepes! The area was bustling with foot traffic, so we expected a long wait, but it ended up being okay. I’m usually not a fan of yogurt in my crepes, but I was content with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding a seat was difficult because the place was crowded, and walking elsewhere to eat wasn’t an option, as it’s culturally considered rude to eat while walking in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Crepe_Diorama.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Crepe_Station.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/sleuths-and-sweets/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/sleuths-and-sweets/</guid>
        
        <category>Dessert</category>
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Airport Ramen at IPPUDO Narita Airport</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I didn’t eat much on the plane. Airplane food has always left a pit in my stomach. I usually eat before my flight or buy a couple of sandwiches before I board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this ramen tasted so good. I don’t know if I was just hungry, but I slurped that noodle and downed the broth. It was really hard to find a place to sit and it was uncomfortably packed. It would be nice if the restaurant could move to a bigger space to accommodate for luggage and seating space. I don’t feel uncomfortable having my luggage outside the restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/airport-ramen-at-ippudo-narita-airport/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/airport-ramen-at-ippudo-narita-airport/</guid>
        
        <category>Ramen</category>
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
